SHELDON: How's this?
"Pleased to meet you, Dr. Gablehauser.
(Sheldon:)How fortunate for you
the university has chosen to hire you...
...despite the fact you've done
no original research in 25 years...
...and instead have written books...
(Sheldon:)...that reduce the great concepts
of science to anecdotes...
(Sheldon:)...each one dumbed down...
(Sheldon:)...to accommodate the duration
of an average bowel movement."
[SPEAKS IN HAWAI IAN]
- "Mahalo" is a nice touch.
- Hmm.
(Sheldon:)Only eight consonants
in the Hawaiian language.
LEONARD:
Interesting, you should lead with that.
(Raj:)Oh, God, look at this buffet.
(Raj:)I love America.
- You don't have buffets in India?
- Of course, but it's all Indian food.
(Raj:)You can't find a bagel in Mumbai
to save your life.
Smear me.
- Well, here's an interesting turn of events.
- What?
(Leonard:)Howard brought a date?
(Sheldon:)A more plausible explanation is that his
work in robotics has made an amazing leap.